{
  "subject":{
    "science":
    [  
     {
       "level1": [
         {
           "question": " science level1 What temperature does water boil at?",
           "optionA": "50 degrees Celcius",
           "optionB": "25 degrees Celcius",
           "optionC": "100 degrees Celcius",
           "optionD": "150 degrees Celcius",
           "answer": "100 degrees Celcius"
         },
 
         {
           "question": " science l2 Who wrote Julius Caesar, Macbeth and Hamlet?",
           "optionA": "Wole Soyinka",
           "optionB": "William Shakespeare",
           "optionC": "Ngozi Chimamanda Adichie",
           "optionD": "Dan Brown",
           "answer": "William Shakespeare"
         },
         {
           "question": "Who wrote Julius Caesar, Macbeth and Hamlet?",
           "optionA": "Wole Soyinka",
           "optionB": "William Shakespeare",
           "optionC": "Ngozi Chimamanda Adichie",
           "optionD": "Dan Brown",
           "answer": "William Shakespeare"
         }
       ],
       "level2": [
         {
           "question": "science l222 What temperature does water boil at?",
           "optionA": "50 degrees Celcius",
           "optionB": "25 degrees Celcius",
           "optionC": "100 degrees Celcius",
           "optionD": "150 degrees Celcius",
           "answer": "100 degrees Celcius"
         },
 
         {
           "question": "Who wrote Julius Caesar, Macbeth and Hamlet?",
           "optionA": "Wole Soyinka",
           "optionB": "William Shakespeare",
           "optionC": "Ngozi Chimamanda Adichie",
           "optionD": "Dan Brown",
           "answer": "William Shakespeare"
         }
       ]
     }],
  "maths":
   [  
    {
      "level1": [
        {
          "question": "maths l11111What temperature does water boil at?",
          "optionA": "50 degrees Celcius",
          "optionB": "25 degrees Celcius",
          "optionC": "100 degrees Celcius",
          "optionD": "150 degrees Celcius",
          "answer": "100 degrees Celcius"
        },

        {
          "question": "Who wrote Julius Caesar, Macbeth and Hamlet?",
          "optionA": "Wole Soyinka",
          "optionB": "William Shakespeare",
          "optionC": "Ngozi Chimamanda Adichie",
          "optionD": "Dan Brown",
          "answer": "William Shakespeare"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who wrote Julius Caesar, Macbeth and Hamlet?",
          "optionA": "Wole Soyinka",
          "optionB": "William Shakespeare",
          "optionC": "Ngozi Chimamanda Adichie",
          "optionD": "Dan Brown",
          "answer": "William Shakespeare"
        }
      ],
      "level2": [
        {
          "question": "maths le22 What temperature does water boil at?",
          "optionA": "50 degrees Celcius",
          "optionB": "25 degrees Celcius",
          "optionC": "100 degrees Celcius",
          "optionD": "150 degrees Celcius",
          "answer": "100 degrees Celcius"
        },

        {
          "question": "Who wrote Julius Caesar, Macbeth and Hamlet?",
          "optionA": "Wole Soyinka",
          "optionB": "William Shakespeare",
          "optionC": "Ngozi Chimamanda Adichie",
          "optionD": "Dan Brown",
          "answer": "William Shakespeare"
        }
      ]
    }]
  }
}
